{
    "subject": "resource/Nina's_Heavenly_Delights",
    "predicate": "ontology/starring",
    "object": "resource/Shelley_Conn",
    "human_readable": "Shelley Conn is starring in Nina's Heavenly Delights.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.899138331413269,
            "question": "Who is starring in Nina's Heavenly Delights?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7816764116287231,
            "question": "Is Shelley Conn an actress?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7406426072120667,
            "question": "What is the name of the movie Shelley Conn is in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7275503873825073,
            "question": "Is Shelley Conn a well-known actress?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7180177569389343,
            "question": "Are there any other actors in Nina's Heavenly Delights?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5362047553062439,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the movie Nina's Heavenly Delights?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5105776786804199,
            "question": "Where can I watch Nina's Heavenly Delights?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4627087414264679,
            "question": "What kind of production is Nina's Heavenly Delights?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4180893301963806,
            "question": "What is the genre of Nina's Heavenly Delights?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3856598734855652,
            "question": "When was Nina's Heavenly Delights released?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Shelley Conn is starring in Nina's Heavenly Delights.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3505_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the genre of Nina's Heavenly Delights?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3505_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of production is Nina's Heavenly Delights?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3505_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can I watch Nina's Heavenly Delights?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3505_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3505_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3505_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3505_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3505_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3505_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3505_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3505_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3505_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3505_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3505_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe text states \"She also played Princess Pondicherry in Charlie and the Chocolate Factory and starred in the 2006 indie film Nina\u2019s Heavenly Delights.\" \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Shelley Conn stars in the film \"Nina's Heavenly Delights,\" which directly supports the statement that Shelley Conn is starring in this movie."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}